MENACHEM HOFFMAN

Address: Sydney, Australia • Mobile: 0401717940

Email: menachemhoffman@outlook.com • LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/menachemhoffman/

CAREER PROFILE

Currently studying computer science with an initial aspiration of becoming become a full stack developer within next the five years. In time, I aim to be a junior backend developer with a particular interest in data science, solving complex problems for people and a strong track record of working with large teams to complete deliverables for programing development

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

Deakin University, Melbourne, Australia

March 2021 - Present

• Learning a range of subject with computer language such as C# with Object-Oriented programming and Python with the data structures course

Diploma of Applied Information Technology

Latrobe University, Melbourne, Australia

September 2019 - January 2021

Received a sound background of computer hardware, computer software and Internet of things devices

Bible Studies

Rabbinical College Of America, Morristown, New Jersey, America

August 2018 - August 2019

- Developed a deeper understanding of the Jewish traditional texts
- Adhered to a rigorous program of study including complex concepts
- Enhanced ability to concentrate for long periods of time
- Absorbed detailed information and learned to practically apply the knowledge

Bible Studies

Rabbinical College of Australia and N.Z., Melbourne, Australia

November 2016 - July 2018

- · Full day study of biblical texts with focus on understanding biblical text to drive meaning for life
- Improved the ability to the ability to learn and study at a more advanced level
- Took part in broad social outreach program and communicated and helped people with a wide spectrum of ages, backgrounds and social status

EXPERIENCE

The Kashrut Authority, Sydney, Australia

November 2019 - Present

Field Supervisor

· Managed clients to ensure their food is up to kosher highest standards for the local community

Kesser Torah College, Sydney, Australia

January 2014 - September 2016

Assistant Network Manager

- Played a role in the school's local area network management team, including the maintenance and troubleshooting of the 100-plus network of personal computers and iPads
- Provided technical assistance with audio-visual presentations at annual school events, including assemblies and speech nights

COMPUTER SKILLS

- Proficient Object Oriented programing in Java and C#
- Informed Relational Databases with AWS in SQL
- Skilled in Web development with HTML, CSS
- Competent with Data Structures in Python
- Proficient in Microsoft Office user
- Experienced working with Mac or PC

PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIPS

Australian Computer Society ASC, Associate Member Membership Number :4288514

March 2021 - Present

- The society provides a variety of services to enable students to increase technical knowledge and capability in computer science including hackathons and local area meetups
- Assists with finding students internships and graduate positions
- The professional society facilitates networking opportunities and training with other data science professionals
- Provides the environment to explore the opportunities in software development space and data science

REFEREES

• Reference available upon request